# JONATHAN WEBER

# WEB DEVELOPER

(C) (760) 419-07<u>34</u>

✓ Jonweber09@gmail.com

🧿 Vista, CA

https://jonweberportfol.io

in Jonweber09

JayWebz

7+ years experienced, dynamic, and diligent Front-end Web Developer with an exemplary history of building, implementing, updating, and managing websites and web applications using objectoriented best practices, usercentric design, and modern programming tools and languages. Such work includes building games, a music playlist-generation web app, and static and dynamic responsive websites. Wellversed in Single-Page Applications, using CMS', and connecting APIs to Web Uls.

#### **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

Web tech & frameworks - HTML5, CSS3, ReactJS, Redux

Scripting - JavaScript, Node.js,

PHP, Python

Debug: Chrome, Firefox

Application/Web Server: Apache

(XAMPP), Webpack

Versioning/Other tools: Git Mercurial, JIRA, Beanstalk,

Sourcetree

Deployment Tools: Jenkins,

Docker

#### **MANAGERIAL SKILLS**

Front-end Development Agile Method Code Optimization **UI** Enhancement Stakeholder MGMT **Documentation & Reporting** 

#### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

NTN Buzztime, Inc. » Web Developer

09/2013 - PRESENT 12/2016 - PRESENT

- > Develop UI/UX across several websites and manage the interchange of data between servers and users using REST/SOAP API calls.
- > Translate UI/UX design wireframes into coded features to build and enhance overall architecture of web applications

» Digital Marketing Manager 08/2015 - 11/2016

- > Developed the front-end of primary website through WordPress CMS with Software Engineer and increased incoming qualified leads by 40% over a four month period.
- > Designed and optimized online marketing & advertising campaigns via search marketing (SEO and PPC), email, and social media.

» Digital Marketing Coordinator 09/2013 - 08/2015

- > Designed responsive landing pages, email templates, banners, and other graphics for use in digital promotions and lead-generation.
- > Managed development schedule to optimize deliverability metrics through enterprise-level Marketing automation software.

**Home Depot** 

04/2008 - 01/2014

- » Head Cashier
- > Trained & managed associates while ultimately maintaining customer satisfaction.
- > Solved in-store computer hardware and store-system technical issues
- > Created weekly store schedule for 130 people to fulfill associate coverage needs.

# TECHNICAL PROJECTS

#### **South Coast Surety**

01/2018 - 11/2018

- > Designed and developed template-based Wordpress website working with backend developer.
  - > ENV: Wordpress/PHP, HTML, Sass, NPM

# Mira Costa College Dance

01/2014 - 05/2014

- > Competed with team and won best web design implemented as new Dance Dept. Website
  - > ENV: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery

### Katie Scoggins Yoga

09/2014 - 12/2014

- > Designed and developed basic website for yoga teacher
- > ENV: static HTML, CSS, jQuery

## **EDUCATION**

# Mira Costa College

> Programming with Python

→ E-Commerce & Web Presence → Mobile Sites & Apps

Site Design & Architecture

#### 01/2014 - 12/2017

- > Web Design: PHP/Wordpress
- JavaScript and jQuery

#### CSU, San Marcos 08/2007 - 05/2012

- > B.S. Business Administration Global Business Management and Marketing, Minor German Language
  - VP, CSUSM Marketing Society
- > Developed and implemented web, email, and social presence for 50 member club.